const gymf_questions = [
  {
    Question: "What colors best describe you or what colors are you looking for in a song?",
    isNumInput: false,
    Answers: ["Red", "Orange", "Yellow", "Green", "Blue", "Indigo", "Violet"],
    Results: [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]
  },
  {
    Question: "How happy are you today on a scale from 0-10?",
    isNumInput: true,
    Answers: ["Quality"],
    Results: [0],
  },
  {
    Question: "What food(s) would you like to have for dinner?",
    isNumInput: false,
    Answers: ["Meat", "Seafood", "Veggies", "Nothing"],
    Results: [0, 0, 0, 0],
  },
  {
    Question: "Which of these animal(s) speak to you?",
    isNumInput: false,
    Answers: ["Elephant", "Fish", "Turtle", "Fox", "Cow", "Dog", "Cat"],
    Results: [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0],
  },
  {
    Question: "Out of these disney movie(s) which do you like?",
    isNumInput: false,
    Answers: ["Star Wars", "Frozen", "Moana", "Hercules", "Raya", "Aladdin"],
    Results: [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0],
  },
  {
    Question: "How was your quality of sleep last night on a scale from 0-10?",
    isNumInput: true,
    Answers: ["Sleep"],
    Results: [0],
  },
  {
    Question: "Did you / will you have fun today?",
    isNumInput: false,
    Answers: ["Yes", "No"],
    Results: [0, 0],
  },
  {
    Question: "Are you being productive right now?",
    isNumInput: false,
    Answers: ["Yes", "No"],
    Results: [0, 0],
  },
  {
    Question: "Do you enjoy rollercoasters?",
    isNumInput: false,
    Answers: ["Yes", "No"],
    Results: [0, 0],
  },
  {
    Question: "What Myers-Briggs Type Indicator(s) are you? (https://www.16personalities.com/personality-types)",
    isNumInput: false,
    Answers: ["Analysts", "Diplomats", "Sentinels", "Explorers"],
    Results: [0, 0, 0, 0],
  },
  {
    Question: "Choose some Astrology/zodiac sign(s) along with yours! (http://nuclear.ucdavis.edu/~rpicha/personal/astrology/)",
    isNumInput: false,
    Answers: ["Aries", "Taurus", "Gemini", "Leo", "Cancer", "Libra", "Virgo", "Scorpio", "Sagittarius", "Capricorn", "Aquarius", "Pisces"],
    Results: [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0],
  },
]

export default gymf_questions